Hi, could you by any chance help me up
the escalator ?
Yeah, that's okay.
My back went out and I'm very scared of
it.
Okay.
Okay, thank you young man. That's very
nice of you.
You're welcome.
What is your name ?
My name is Giovanni.
Hi Giovanni.
What's your name ?
Three, two, one.
My name is Lucy.
Nice to meet you, Miss Lucy.
Nice to meet you.
You're very nice to do this. Now, did you
come to the mall to buy something ?
Yes.
What are you trying to get today ?
Probably some shoes. I've been needing
some new shoes.
Oh, new shoes. How old are you ?
I'm thirteen.
Thirteen. Oh, you're a very nice young
man.
Oh, no, no, no.
It's okay.
Oh, thank you. Thank you young man.
You're welcome.
That is very nice of you.
Oh, you know what ?
I have to tell you nobody else helped me.
No one else did.
That's a shame.
That is very nice of you. You're the one
person that really helped me.
I'd like to give you something, okay ?
Okay.
This is a thousand dollars.
A thousand dollars ?
Yes. I want you to take that.
Yes. You go buy your shoes.
A thousand dollars ?
Give me a hug.
What ?
A thousand dollars.
Thank you so much.
You're welcome.
I've never seen this much money in my
entire lifetime.
Well, I hope it helps you, okay ?
And I hope you have a good day. Why did
you help me ?
I just felt like it was a good deed. I
saw you came up to me, so obviously you
really must need help. So I helped you.
Yes.
I got a good income. This is crazy. I
mean, this is insane.
But that's what you get for good deeds,
young man.
My heart is beating so fast right now. I
don't even know what to think right now.
All right. Well, I'll give you another
hug.